<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on micsthepick&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>https://micsthepick.github.io/blog/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on micsthepick&#39;s blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://micsthepick.github.io/blog/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The truth heals</title>
      <link>https://micsthepick.github.io/blog/post/the_truth_heals/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://micsthepick.github.io/blog/post/the_truth_heals/</guid>
      <description>You may have been told the truth hurts. Maybe you resonate with this in a very deep and personal way. I&amp;rsquo;m not here to say that the truth is harmless, in fact is it quite the opposite. Jesus in the bible says that his word is a sharp &amp;ldquo;double-edged sword&amp;rdquo;, Whether you believe the bible to be a source of solely truth or even the sole source of absolute truth, the sentiment still stands &amp;ldquo;The truth hurts&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IR and RF remote hacking</title>
      <link>https://micsthepick.github.io/blog/post/ir_rf_remote_hacking/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://micsthepick.github.io/blog/post/ir_rf_remote_hacking/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this blog post, I will describe the methods I used to remote control various devices by spoofing Infrared (IR) and Radio Frequency (RF) signals, i.e. a basic replay attack.
Vulnerable devices Not all devices will be vulnerable to this style of attack, for example, modern car key fobs will use rolling codes or some more sophisticated form of attack that only lets one code be used once. However common home items such as TVs, DVD players, Fans and Lights will likely be vulnerable to this attack (but since they are not likely to get stolen from this attack, it&amp;rsquo;s not a huge security concern more than a nuisance, and most likely you could just buy the same remote from another device and use that already)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://micsthepick.github.io/blog/post/fixing_my_wifi_adpater/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://micsthepick.github.io/blog/post/fixing_my_wifi_adpater/</guid>
      <description>Fixing my Wifi Adapter I happen to have a TP Link Branded Adapter (T3U, but this fix should work on a variety of devices) It turns out that a common problem is that it doesn&amp;rsquo;t use USB 3, and when I create a PAN (personal area network) - even if I set it to prefer 5GHz, the speed was abysmally slow.
I searched for quite a while for a fix, and finally stumbled on this beta driver from this TP-LINK post: [https://community.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
